# STEFAN DJORDJEVIC

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

## CONTACT

Belgrade, Serbia

+381656200703

stdj.1907@gmail.com

# EDUCATION

Belgrade institute of Technology (BIT bootcamp)

Graduated December 2020

## **SKILLS & TOOLS**

- HTML
- CSS (Bootstrap)
- SASS
- JavaScript
- JQuery
- React
- GIT
- Wordpress
- Firebase
- Photoshop

## LANGUAGE

- English (Proficient)
- Spanish (intermediate)

## ABOUT ME

- High social skills
- Disciplined
- Problem solving skills
- Flexible
- Responsible
- Dedicated
- Teamwork skills
- Creative
- Patient

### SUMMARY

Front-end Web Developer with 2 years of experience in website and web application developing. Collaborative, attentive and customer oriented, my experience is in turning customers' wishes into perfect projects. I redesigned over 70 webpages and added some functionality to them.

## EXPERIENCE

Front-End Web Developer

• Jan 2020 -Jun 2021

#### Fiverr - Freelance Services

Repairing web applications also working as technical support. Implementing new features to existing web applications. Creating landing pages, SEO optimisation.

Junior Front-End Web Developer

Jun 2020 - Dec 2020

#### Twilo Creative - Pontefract, United Kingdom

Optimizing and debugging web projects across screen sizes, browsers, mobile/desktop. Proposing functional improvements to new or existing projects. Redesigning over 70 webpages using 60% WordPress (Elementor) and 40% HTML/CSS/JavaScript.

Internship Front-end Developer

Nov 2019 - Jun 2020

#### Casepoint Pvt. Ltd. - Surat, India

Working on smaller projects, while the mentor was monitoring my performance, answering the questions and solving misunderstandings on a daily basis.

# PROJECTS - click to visit project

MASSAGE SALON | WEB DESIGNER & CREATOR
 Technologies used: WordPress • Elemenotr builder • SQL

MESSAGE CHAT | GIT REPOSITORY

Technologies used: HTML • CSS • JavaScript • React • Firebase

BUDGET CONTROLLER | GIT REPOSITORY

Technologies used: HTML • CSS • JavaScript • DOM • MVC pattern

• <u>DICE GAME</u> | <u>GIT REPOSITORY</u>

Technologies used: HTML • CSS • JavaScript • DOM

SOUNDPROOF MUSIC ORGANIZATION

In progress